[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 5 and height 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "2.5",
      "options": [
        "5.0",
        "6.5",
        "2.5",
        "0.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 2 and height 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "8.0",
      "options": [
        "8.0",
        "10.5",
        "12.0",
        "5.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 1 and height 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "1.0",
      "options": [
        "1.0",
        "-1.5",
        "5.0",
        "3.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 5 and height 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "15.0",
      "options": [
        "12.5",
        "17.5",
        "15.0",
        "19.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 1 and height 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "1.5",
      "options": [
        "4.0",
        "5.5",
        "-1.0",
        "1.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 6 and height 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "27.0",
      "options": [
        "24.5",
        "29.5",
        "27.0",
        "31.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 7 and height 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "17.5",
      "options": [
        "20.0",
        "17.5",
        "21.5",
        "15.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 2 and height 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "1.0",
      "options": [
        "5.0",
        "-1.5",
        "1.0",
        "3.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 9 and height 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "36.0",
      "options": [
        "36.0",
        "38.5",
        "33.5",
        "40.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 8 and height 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "28.0",
      "options": [
        "25.5",
        "32.0",
        "30.5",
        "28.0"
      ]
    }
]